#### Contact

ntuano@pegasus.rutgers.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/nancy-t-41067a6 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Nursing

**PALS** 

Healthcare

#### Languages

Tagalog (Native or Bilingual)

#### Certifications

Stroke Certified Registered Nurse (SCRN)
CCRN

# Nancy Tuano

#### RN BSN CCRN SCRN

Greater San Diego Area

## Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Surgical-Neuro Intensive Care Unit. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (B.S.) focused in Nursing from Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey-Newark.

## Experience

Sharp HealthCare

9 years

Registered Nurse

July 2015 - Present (5 years)

Greater San Diego Area

Surgical Intensive Care Unit

#### Registered Nurse II

July 2011 - July 2015 (4 years 1 month)

Greater San Diego Area

**Progressive Care Unit** 

Hackensack University Medical Center

Registered Nurse II

December 2009 - July 2011 (1 year 8 months)

hackensack, new jersey

Medical Surgical

New York Eye and Ear Infirmary of Mount Sinai

Registered Nurse

June 2008 - November 2009 (1 year 6 months)

new york, new york

Urgent Care, Ambulatory Care

Jersey City Medical Center Registered Nurse December 2004 - December 2007 (3 years 1 month)

Jersey City, New Jersey

Medical Surgical

## Education

Rutgers, The State University of New Jersey-Newark Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Nursing · (2005 - 2011)

Holy Name Hospital School of Nursing
Associate of Arts and Sciences (AAS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2002 - 2004)

Saint Peter's University
Associate of Arts and Sciences - AAS, Nursing · (2002 - 2004)